Tufts Weekly UP056
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 4, 1966; UP056.001.060.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Academic Honors; p.1.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 10, 1966; UP056.001.060.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Academic Honors; pp.1,9. [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Wins interfraternity council trivia contest.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 18, 1966; UP056.001.060.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 60)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Alex Elias Memorial Scholarship Fund benefits [concert].
  - Tufts Weekly, December 2, 1966; UP056.001.060.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Donald G. Abbott (1944) (Adm). Director of Office of Publications (includes photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, December 9, 1966; UP056.001.060.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 16, 1966; UP056.001.060.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 60)
    [Phillip A. Anderson] [A1968] Concert Jazz Band Leader [incl. photo]; Donald Altvater [A1967] co-captain of Wrestling team [photo]
  - Tufts Weekly, January 4, 1967; UP056.001.060.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 6, 1967; UP056.001.060.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 60)
    [Donald Altvater] co-captain of wrestling team [photo]
  - Tufts Weekly, February 3, 1967; UP056.001.060.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 10, 1967; UP056.001.060.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 17, 1967; UP056.001.060.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Richard Alpert [A1952] Leads LSD movement with Timothy Leary [incl. photo].
  - Tufts Weekly, February 24, 1967; UP056.001.060.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 3, 1967; UP056.001.060.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 60)
    [Admissions] Undergraduate admissions: an overview. p. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 10, 1967; UP056.001.060.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Phillip A. Anderson [A1968] Concert Jazz Band Leader [incl. photo].
  - Tufts Weekly, March 17, 1967; UP056.001.060.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Donald Altvater [A1967] student council representative in charge of Parents' weekend [includes photo]
  - Tufts Weekly, March 31, 1967; UP056.001.060.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 7, 1967; UP056.001.060.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Donald G. Abbott (1944) (Adm). Course catalogue delayed (includes photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, April 14, 1967; UP056.001.060.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 60)
    [Admissions] Forum on policy. p. 9.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 21, 1967; UP056.001.060.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 28, 1967; UP056.001.060.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 5, 1967; UP056.001.060.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 60)
    Academic Honors; pp.1,3. Freeland Abbott (faculty). Appointed to Board of the Experimental College (includes photo).
  - Tufts Weekly, May 12, 1967; UP056.001.060.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 60)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 18, 1967; UP056.001.061.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 22, 1967; UP056.001.061.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 61)
    Freeland K. Abbott, Injured in auto accident, p. 4.
  - Tufts Weekly, September 29, 1967; UP056.001.061.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 61)
    Adminstration 1967-68. Changes in,
  - Tufts Weekly, October 6, 1967; UP056.001.061.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 61)
    Adminstration 1967. Development Office (includes photo of Frank Tredenick).
  - Tufts Weekly, October 20, 1967; UP056.001.061.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 61)
    Adminstration 1967. Denies relevance of "in low parentis" at Tufts.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 27, 1967; UP056.001.061.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 27 Megabytes (Box 61)
    [Afro-American Society] Activities, p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 3, 1967; UP056.001.061.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 27 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 10, 1967; UP056.001.061.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 26 Megabytes (Box 61)
    [Afro-American Society] Activities, p. 10.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 17, 1967; UP056.001.061.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 27 Megabytes (Box 61)
    Academic Honors; Awards; pp.1,9; [American association of university professors] Views student rights
  - Tufts Weekly, December 1, 1967; UP056.001.061.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 26 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 8, 1967; UP056.001.061.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 25 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 15, 1967; UP056.001.061.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 12, 1968; UP056.001.061.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 21 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 9, 1968; UP056.001.061.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 27 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 16, 1968; UP056.001.061.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 28 Megabytes (Box 61)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Awarded President's Trophy [incl. photo].
  - Tufts Weekly, February 23, 1968; UP056.001.061.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 1, 1968; UP056.001.061.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 21 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 8, 1968; UP056.001.061.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 23 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 15, 1968; UP056.001.061.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 22, 1968; UP056.001.061.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 1, 1968; UP056.001.061.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 23 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 12, 1968; UP056.001.061.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 19 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 19, 1968; UP056.001.061.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 61)
    [Admissions] Aid officers point to lack of funds (incl. photo of Dean John C. Palmer). p. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 26, 1968; UP056.001.061.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 18 Megabytes (Box 61)
    [Admissions] Aid officers point to lack of funds (incl. photo of Dean John C. Palmer). pp. 1, 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 3, 1968; UP056.001.061.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 61)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 10, 1968; UP056.001.061.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 26 Megabytes (Box 61)
    [Afro-American Society] Activities, p. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, September 9, 1968; UP056.001.062.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 62)
    Administration 1968. Changes in,
  - Tufts Weekly, September 13, 1968; UP056.001.062.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 20, 1968; UP056.001.062.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 62)
    Academic Calendar, 1968-69, New University Calendar, p. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 4, 1968; UP056.001.062.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 11, 1968; UP056.001.062.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 18, 1968; UP056.001.062.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 62)
    Academic Ceremonies 1968. Experimental degree sought by Experimental College.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 25, 1968; UP056.001.062.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 1, 1968; UP056.001.062.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 8, 1968; UP056.001.062.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 62)
    [Adler, Richard] Zeroxography. P. 3.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 15, 1968; UP056.001.062.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 23 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 22, 1968; UP056.001.062.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 28 Megabytes (Box 62)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 6, 1968; UP056.001.062.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 62)
- Tufts Weekly, 1902 -- 1917; UP056.002.GB (Box 1)
  microfilm reel, not yet processed. Former barcode 39090015515931g